{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1068","name":"Burger King","address":"17440 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224","owner":"EYM King of Michigan LLC","licenseNumber":"078356","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-82.92512,42.40750","geojson":{"id":"1068","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.9251207309999,42.407495393]},"properties":{"name":"Burger King","owner":"EYM King of Michigan LLC","address":"17440 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"078356","establishmentid":"1068","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"6/6/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2268","name":"High Noon Saloon","address":"17339 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"4467","name":"Big Burgzs","address":"17627 E Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1992","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"17140 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"4412","name":"East English Village Preparatory Academy","address":"5020 Cadieux","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622709","name":"Wing Snob Detroit","address":"17101 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622784","name":"York Sussex Partners","address":"17017 E Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5172","name":"Danny's Diner","address":"17017 E Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"318","name":"Cadieux Cafe","address":"4300 Cadieux  Rd","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"418","name":"East English Village Bar & Grill","address":"16915 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2466","name":"Pizza Hut #26290","address":"16835 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622460","name":"Starbuck's Coffee Company","address":"18051 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622566","name":"ESH Ice Arena","address":"4831 Canyon","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"2813","name":"Bogartz Food and Spirits","address":"17441 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"4405","name":"McDonald's","address":"18201 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"3184","name":"Trolley's","address":"17315 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"3195","name":"La Cina","address":"17201 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2266","name":"Dish","address":"18441 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"51622780","name":"Side Dish","address":"18441 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"1595","name":"Rabaut's Cafe","address":"18536 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"1116","name":"Marquette Elementary School (Annex)","address":"6145 Canyon","zipcode":"48236"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43526","inspectionDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Ice bin","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-09-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41955","inspectionDate":"2018-04-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"At the Dumpster enclosure","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40330","inspectionDate":"2017-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DRIVE-THRU WINDOW","subLocation":"On the bottom Shelf","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"38344","inspectionDate":"2017-03-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36624","inspectionDate":"2016-10-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"DRIVE-THRU WINDOW","subLocation":"At the Sink (dump)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"At the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1068"}}